[Music]
[Música]
If I stay, put the blanket here,
si me quedo pone la mantita aquí de
grandpa, right now it was really cold all of a
abuelo ya mismo hacía mucho frío de
sudden, no,
repente no
suddenly, here in Seville, there are
de repente aquí el sevilla es que
three or four more seasons, it's
existen tres estaciones de más o cuatro
summer and winter, the season of
es el verano invierno la estación de
Santa Justa and San Bernardo, I mean, there's
santa justa y la de san bernardo o sea
no more, it's good if the one in Plaza
no hay más es bueno si la de la de plaza
de Almas is true, yes, it's real, but
de almas verdad si es de verdad pero
we go from the cold to the heat, suddenly it's
pasamos del frío el calor de repente es
spring, autumn and so on, little by
primavera otoño y demás poquito a
little, well, let's see an excerpt from a
poquito bueno vamos a ver un extracto de
live show in which he's apparently
directo en el que ya aquí al parecer
talking about me, watch out,
habla de mí
the night is very calm, man,
ojo que la noche está muy tranqui tío
watch out, at night we're calm and very
ojo que la noche estamos tranquilo y muy
chill, here talking with my
del chill aquí hablando con mi
kids, having a good time and so on, I hope there's
chavalería de buen rollo y demás espero
no bad vibes,
que no haya ningún mal rollo
350, okay,
350 avale
doesn't come out to me, 350,
no me sale 350
how do they do it on the hour, 350, on the live show
como hacen en la hora 350 en el directo
now on the air,
de ahora aire
I'm a person who needs a lot of
yo soy una persona que necesita mucho de
state aid, let's see,
las ayudas del estado a ver a lo mejor
maybe it's in another live show, not in which 350 does
es que es en otro directo no en que 350
n't fit, it doesn't
no me cuadra
fit in 350 on the air,
no me cuadra en 350 aire
350 doesn't fit in,
350 no me cuadra
there's between 50 and  It could be if the
hay de entre el 50 no puede ser si el
live lasts 2 hours,
directo dura 2 horas
there you go, these guys just made
hay dejarlas estos tíos acaba de liar
a lot of noise
muchísimo aire
now 50 in the live broadcast of the south but how is it
ahora 50 en el directo del sur pero como
going to be the director of Chubut to see the
va a ser el director del chubut a ver en
live broadcast of the south
directo del sur
that freedom is for
que la libertad está a
no one to tell you anything and I feel very
nadie decirte nada y yo me siento muy
good that they make the south in call I
bien que te hagan el sur en llamada
accept surf
acepto surf
that I accept 8 you are going to make me throw 5
que acepte 8 me vas a hacer a echarme 5
payments he is
pagos
going to make me throw the 5 for you
me va a hacer a echarme el 5 para vos
but you because you are in a paid live broadcast I do
pero tú porque estás en directo de pago
not understand
no lo entiendo
but why is
pero porque está en un directo de pago
the south in a paid live broadcast is that I do not understand it
el sur es que no entiendo
can be seen in Giacchino's live broadcast
se puede ver en el directo de giacchino
equally not
igualmente no
the height brand that of the
la marca altura la de la laguna del
Dallas lagoon putting his live broadcast for members I
dallas poniendo su directo para miembros
do it but not while you are
lo hago pero no mientras que estás en
live
directo
but it is not that it is live I
pero no me está que está en directo la
throw it to see it but it can be seen from
echó a ver pero se puede ver en él desde
here no longer
aquí ya no
the equation is the same and it
la ecuación es la misma y
can be seen from here and but of course I
se puede ver desde aquí y pero claro que
have to
tengo que
what minutes
a qué minutos
I am screwing my life man
me estoy jodiendo la vida tío
here is all because this I am already with
aquí es todo porque esto ya me estoy con
my things my concern is we do not
mis cosas mi preocupación es podemos no
have your concern is in the end I
tiene su preocupación es al final yo
think that it repeats itself a little  but if it's that
creo que se repita un poquito pero si es
I don't know if you tell me to be like I
que yo no sé si tú me dices que sea como
apologize it seems to me
pido disculpas me parece
here I don't
aquí no
have much pressure I
tengo mucha presión
can't develop my
no puedo desarrollar mi
live show because I feel super natural and
directo pues me siento súper natural y
I told him as I have always been
se lo dije como como he sido yo siempre
no and why from what people have
no y por qué por lo que la gente me ha
known me but yes they are going to smoke me all the
conocido pero si me van a fumar todo el
time
rato
but well in the end I think that I have already
pero bueno al final yo creo que ya me he
known a lot of that bubble of much
sabido mucho de esa burbuja de
much calmer
mucho más tranquilo
because I am literally prohibited is
porque estoy literalmente prohibido es
the word because I would make more jokes and
la palabra porque haría que más bromas y
such but I say 40 talks saying that I do
tal pero digo 40 talks diciendo que me
n't like it came something like that
cae mal vino algo así
why
eso por qué
cut I think the same guy who
recortados yo creo que el mismo tipo que
is a big problem honestly because
es un gran problema honestamente porque
the worst thing is that well people people
lo peor es que bueno la gente la gente
are
es
terrible about age to see the
terrible sobre edad para ver cabrón el
live show and then if you are going to give your opinion on
directo y luego si vas a opinar sobre
something like that I already recorded like I know
algo así que ya grabé en plan yo que sé
of a relationship or anything more or
de una relación o cualquier cosa más o
less but people did not
menos pero la gente no lo
comment on it not about many things since there are
comenté no de muchas cosas ya que hay
things that I do not fully believe the
cosas que no me termino de creer el
bush and such and I see that they were taken out
arbusto y tal y veo que estaban sacadas
of context or whatever or it is to stir up
de contexto o lo que sea o es para meter
[ __ ] and there are things the comments that you
[__] y hay movidas los comentarios que
flip out and such but well this week
flipas y tal pero bueno esta semana
you be careful  you've eaten a lot today it's this
cuidada tú has comido mucho hoy es esta
week the ball I wasn't watching and
semana la pelotita yo no estaba viendo y
juani with adital
juani con adital
this month and
este mes y
especially our thing
sobre todo lo nuestro
of 8
de 8
with this it's late but it seems like a bad
con esto es tarde pero me parece mala
idea it doesn't seem like a bad idea but but he seems
idea es no me parece mala idea pero pero
stressed he seems
se le nota estresado se le note
stressed because he has said some things that I
estresado porque ha dicho unas cosas que
think he would not have said in
yo creo que él no hubiese dicho de
any way why is it
ninguna manera por qué es
in the end with what has happened to you to
al final con lo que te ha pasado a
ticket they have called all kinds of guys that you
ticket han llamado de todo tío que tú
call another person that's that like that I
llames a otra persona eso eso así en eso
agree with you because I think
coincido contigo porque creo que
we will get that Dallas is not a he
conseguiremos con que dallas no es un no
is not stupid he is a guy who is not stupid and he
es tonto es un tío que no es tonto y
knows very well that those types of
sabe de sobra que ese tipo de
comments or saying those types of things in
comentarios o decir ese tipo de cosas en
a live broadcast of
un directo
course because he is the first one
claro obviamente porque es el primero
that he has defended tooth and nail for
que ha defendido a capa y espada durante
years and look at how much he has suffered from being
años y mira que ha sufrido de que lo han
called that same thing without any kind of
llamado eso mismo sin ningún tipo de
proof simply because such and of course I
prueba simplemente porque tal y claro yo
think he got heated day then I I
creo que se calentó día entonces yo yo
think that is a little he has commented
creo que ese es un poco ha comentado
particularly that he had been sleeping very
particulamente que venía durmiendo muy
little I don't know how long I am not several
poco no sé cuánto tiempo no soy varios
months and such if it
meses y tal si no
is not late or he has him very stressed and in the
es tarde o lo tiene muy estresado y al
end we feel  that each one as it is what
final nos sentimos que cada uno como es
happened I think that in the end
lo que se dio yo creo que al final
when I said it and I commented on it live
cuando yo lo dije y lo comenté en
live when you have a
directo en directo cuando tú tienes un
friend the same or I mean me yes one day I
amigo lo mismo o sea yo sí yo un día me
forgive myself get along with Javi imagine that
perdono llévese con javi imagínate que
we talk one day and we forgive each other man one
hablamos un día y nos perdonamos tío una
thing is that he forgives me with Javi another
cosa es que me perdone con javi otra
thing is that he talks to me and they
cosa que me que me hable y le den al
answer him like friends forever you
contestar rollo amigos para siempre
know I think I think
sabes creo que creo que
the [ __ ] up
la putada
in the end friends are scarce
al final los amigos escasean
and there are many times that you feel alone
y hay muchas veces que te sientes solo
just because it happened
sólo porque ha pasado
and I think Dallas was very stressed out
y creo que dallas estaba muy estresado
and it gives me like thanks
dio y me da como gracias
sometimes for texts about everything and I
a veces por textos sobre todo tal y le
see him and it's that it makes me a little bit of it makes me
veo y es que me da un poquito de me da
quite sorry man because I
bastante pena tío porque yo
think that I could have talked to him
creo que podría haber hablado con el
Dallas that day
dallas ese día
yes it's true that I didn't want to and I was just
sí que es verdad que no quería y yo solo
putting it in and no but I could have talked to
metía y no pero podría haber hablado con
her the best and well the atmosphere was
ella lo mejor y bueno estaba el ambiente
tense the truth is to be able to debate
tenso la verdad es de poder debate
with me I don't know if it would have been a good
conmigo no sé si hubiera sido buen
time for the two of them to talk
momento para que hablara los dos
[Music]
[Música]
would have come out its virality participate in
hubieran salió su viralidad participa en
that moment
ese momento
its virality and if  I like to see a
su viralidad y si me gusta ver una
person's place, I
persona sitio
think he was
yo creo que tenía ilusión por estar
very excited about his project, of course, and I think
muchísimo su proyecto claro y yo creo
that when he sees that someone answers him
que cuando ve que alguien o le contesta
and such, I think they took a wild look at him, I think it
y tal yo creo que se les fue una mirada
was an
del incendio creo que fue una mina de
ink mine, I think this shouldn't happen
tinta creo que no debería haber esto eso
because I don't think he has anything against
porque no creo que tenga nada en contra
him
de él
and he doesn't answer me either, I mean,
y a mí no me contesta tampoco o sea yo a
sometimes I talk to him and don't do that with
veces le hablo y no hagas eso con todo
everyone, the other day he spoke to me so
el mundo el otro día me habló para
anyone who talks to him knows he
cualquiera que hable con él sabe que
does that all the time, but let's see, it's
hace eso siempre pero a ver yo es que
not common, let's see, he's a colleague, I
poco común a ver es un colega le tengo
appreciate him, I like
aprecio me cae bien
the kid, maybe a couple of times I
el chaval a lo mejor un par de veces le
asked him for a couple of things and he gave them to me,
pedí un par de cosas y me las ha dado
but then it's true that we can't
pero luego sí que verdad que no podemos
say that we're best friends, they
decir que seamos amiguísimos que me
're ignoring me, everything I tell you, he does
están ignorando todo lo que te digo que
n't talk to me, but not because a person,
no me habla pero no porque una persona
a colleague, a colleague from work, thanks,
un colega un colega del trabajo gracias
stir up
revolver
this day, that's why you're
este día
not going to put on a fuss you know,
por eso no vas a montar la de dios sabes
but neither you nor any other person
pero ni tú ni cualquier otra persona
is also a respectable content
también es un contenido respetable
is behind everything that
está detrás de todo lo que
happens, neither do I sometimes when
pasa yo tampoco hay a veces que me habla
people talk to me, I don't answer, I say because this is already
la gente no contesto digo porque esto ya
eating me up, it happens to me  every day I
me estoy comiendo me pasa todos los días
mean I don't answer many people
o sea yo no le contesto a mucha gente
priorities or time that have my
prioridades o tiempo que tenga mis
worries because when you have
preocupaciones por cuando tienes
worries
preocupaciones
I think it gets a little bit itchy but
yo creo que se le pica un poquito pero
if it is that I don't know if you tell me that it
si es que yo no sé si tú me dices que
is as he has apologized and such it
sea como ha pedido disculpas y tal me
seems fine to me and that he has apologized let's
parece bien y que ha pedido disculpas ya
see how the stage goes for him I
ver qué tal le sale el estadio yo me
put the other coffee fault who has
metí el otro café culpa quién ha pedido
apologized and refers to it does not work well
disculpas y se refiere no funciona bien
a good project
un buen proyecto
many years many jobs and like everything
muchos años muchos trabajos y como todo
like everything in this life a project that
como todo en esta vida un proyecto que
in the end is competition youtube to the
al final es competencia youtube al
module that has next to it is called
módulo que tiene al lado se llama
youtube they also know you are in the people but
youtube igual saben sos en la gente pero
here he has referred to that if you
aquí se ha referido con que si tú me
tell me that he is apologized who has
dices que está disculpado quien se ha
apologized because when it comes to preferring
disculpado porque a la hora de preferir
one page or another well evidently he
una página u otra pues evidentemente
is saying he has never apologized
está diciendo nunca ha pedido disculpas
for anything okay that I am a lot of nothing
por nada vale que estoy mucho de nada
if I had slept or rather that a long
si había dormido o sea que ya mucho
time sleeping little and such but those are
tiempo durmiendo poco y tal pero eso son
things that his live tells but I mean he
cosas que cuenta su directo pero o sea
is not sorry for what he
que no está arrepentido de lo que le
said to 8 no no for nothing else on twitter he
dijo a 8 no no para nada más en twitter
was answering this reaffirming it you
estuvo contestando a esto reafirmando lo
know I mean
sabes o sea
I do not want to get involved  in this the only thing
yo no me quiero meter en esto lo único
I pronounced for grande area and juan
que me pronuncié para grande área y juan
because they seem to me to be a
porque me parecen unas una persona de
[ __ ] great person and it has to be said, I mean, I don't think I don't think that
putísima madre y hay que decirlo o sea
everything that was what was being
no creo no creo que sea justo todo lo
done to
que estaba lo que se estaba haciendo de
them is fair, the truth is and I'm going to do it
ellos la verdad y me lo voy a hacer
now, I don't care who it is, I'm
ahora me da igual que quien sea yo a mis
going to defend my friends and I'm
amigos lo voy a defender y a mí la gente
going to defend the people I love to the death
que quiero yo lo voy a defender a muerte
and that's it
y ya está
with pm in wars with people that I don't care about
con pm en guerras con gente que no me va
or come across
ni me viene
the last one, the last one that was with javi, you
la última la última que fue con javi
know, I already said it for a
realmente sabes ya dije yo
long time and
mucho tiempo y
not about a problem, in fact, the other day,
no de un problema de hecho el otro día
well, two months ago, binner, tribute to
bueno hace dos meses binner homenaje a
javier,
javier
but it's
pero es
you, anyone would put it in the
usted lo pondría cualquiera en el
cayenne, a lie, of
cayenne mentira
course you're wrong, I mean, someone went
claro está equivocado o sea alguien fue
to Jackie's chat to tell her that they
a el chat de jackie a decirle que me
had closed my channel, that's
habían cerrado a mí el canal
why already here in the last one, the last one
por eso ya aquí en la último el último
that we reacted to yours, who was
que reaccionamos suyo que precisamente
also talking about the subject of whether with
hablaba también del tema de que si con
javi, whether
javi de que si no
two or three weeks they
dos o tres semanas
told me that
me han dicho que
I do
yo
n't want anyone to be
no quiero que a nadie se le
asked, but when I saw it, no, it didn't
pregunta pero cuando la vi no tampoco la
stop her from the south,
para el sur
but at the moment I'm going to change, nor
pero al momento voy a cambiar a mí ni
from the right in  chur is a little south
del derecho en chur está un poco el sur
being the south
siendo el sur
lethal another one telling how they told him that
letal otra contando como le contaron que
aviles was the channel a couple of months ago and it's
avilés era el canal un par de meses y
south
está al sur
really in a second of change the mini
a verdad en un segundo de cambio la mini
of the live that they just sent me on
del directo que me acaban de mandar al
air
aire
so that this is with complete quality
para que quede esto con completa calidad
with the quality that my content deserves
con la calidad que merece mi contenido
we are doing everything very correct
estamos haciéndolo todo muy correcto
lately his thumbnails in the
últimamente sus miniaturas en los
rights everything is very good
derechos todo muy bien
doing his job he is doing what
haciendo su trabajo está haciendo lo que
he knows and I don't want them to close the
él sabe y no quiero que le cierren el
guy's channel no matter how much indifference you
canal al tío por mucha indiferencia que
have I'm not going to be happy that they
tengas no voy a alegrar de que le
try to screw up his work a person
intenten [__] el trabajo una persona
gave and I know in case one day we have to
dio y a mí sabe por si algún día tenemos
talk and we apologize
que hablar y pedimos disculpas
forgive us for being crazy what happens is that
perdonarnos a mí de locos lo que pasa
at that moment I felt very
que en aquel momento me sentí muy
cornered and online
acorralado y online
no let's see I have no problem what
no a ver yo no tengo problema lo que me
happens to me here is not something super like that
pasa aquí no es algo súper en plan que
sincerely apart from me you already know
sinceramente aparte conmigo ya lo sabéis
rehearsals a person who goes through a bit of
ensayos una persona que pasa un poco de
everything unless it's something personal in
todo a no ser que sea algo personal en
plants involved with my family knows like
plantas metido con mi familia sabe en
something with me who fixes
plan algo conmigo quien arregla las
things with him who fixes things
cosas con él quien arregla las cosas
because he doesn't want to okay that's what happened well
porque no quiere vale que es lo que pasó
in my opinion before  I say it
pues en mi opinión antes de que lo diga
he obeyed I think that the conversation in the
él obedeció yo creo que la charla en
first place in the first
primer lugar en primer en primer
instance neither he nor I had any
instancia ni él ni yo teníamos
idea that it was going to end like this I
pensamiento de que iba a acabar así yo
but I think that we are going to debate
me pero yo me creo que vamos a debatir
a little exchange ideas even if they were
un poco intercambiar ideas aunque fueran
contrary even if they were contrary you know
contrarias aunque fueran contrarias sabe
but in plan it will not end without a plan he has
pero en plan no acabará sin plan tiene
like for example with who I tell you
como por ejemplo con quien te digo yo
at least a conversation like the one I had with
al menos una charla como la que tuve con
Aura of course because there we started
aura por supuesto porque ahí partíamos
from the basis that there was a good vibe
de la base de que había un buen rollo
you know and with Jackie they were not bad
sabes y con jackie no estuvieron mal
vibes but to say that we already had
rollo pero decir que ya contábamos con
the idea that we were going to consider
con la idea de que íbamos a plantearnos
and contrary ideas
e ideas contrarias
and that I was going to put it to him because I had
y que yo iba a ponerle porque le había
made the criticism is because I was
hecho la crítica es porque le estaba
calling him false and such no that is the problem
diciendo falso y tal no ahí el problema
that I saw that he became too
que yo le vi que se puso demasiado
aggressive you know he became too
atacante sabe él se puso demasiada
attacking as if I wanted to
atacante como si yo lo quisiera
corner him or if like with Quesada the saint
acorralar o si como con quesada el santo
5 with Quesada look, with Quesada I
5 con quesada fíjate yo con quesada
argue in front of the public head a
discuto de cara al público cabeza un
live with him is to argue but
directo con él es para discutir pero
then private I get along perfectly
luego privado yo me llevo perfectamente
with Quesada because it is not a
con quesada porque es que no es un tema
personal matter you understand me  in the end we have to
personal me entendéis al final aquí hay
come here to make content to enjoy ourselves
que venir a hacer contenido a disfrutar
to be a while if I have to
a estar un rato si yo tenemos que
debate and discuss about the whole thing but in the
debatir y discutir del rollo pero al
end Tamaki doing work content out
final tamaki haciendo trabajo contenido
of hand no no as something personal
de mano fuera no no como algo personal
that I turn off the computer and I have a
que yo apaga el ordenador y me tiene el
grudge against people I don't know if it's something like super
rencor con la gente a no sé que sea algo
that really hurts me like what
que me duela de verdad en plan como me
people that you know have done to me or things
ha hecho gente que ustedes saben o cosas
that have attacked my family
que han atacada mi familia
things already personal attacks no to people
cosas ya ataques personales no a gente
who have even tried
que ha intentado incluso joderme la vida
to screw up my life screw up my job [ __ ] in many ways no me what hurt me about Jackie was that it was that he got upset not that he insulted me yes it's true that later I would also have to watch the debate again to see in what order
ver el debate para ver en qué orden
things go because I never
transcurre las cosas porque nunca me
saw that debate again it
volvía a ver ese debate
is an edited version that the editor made for me
es una versión editada que me hizo el
but I never saw that
editor pero yo nunca volví a ver ese
debate again I would have to see how
debate tendría que ver cómo transcurre
the thing goes but if it is as I
la movida pero si es tal y como yo lo
remember it I was like taking
recuerdo yo como que le estaba sacando
things out of him because I saw him as a hypocrite because he was
cosas de porque le veía hipócrita porque
not right and he was like he was
no tenía la razón y él como que estaba
very defensive because he believed that
muy a la defensiva porque se creía que
I was going  to humiliate Leo attack him or something to
yo iba a humillar leo atacarle o algo a
laugh at something like that he didn't get
reírme de algo por el estilo no se puso
very
muy
aggressive
agresivo
very attacking very aggressive I don't know then
muy atacante muy agresiva no sé entonces
he grabbed at a mistake that I had like a burning nail
agarró como un clavo ardiendo a un error
which is a mistake and it is not a
que tuve yo que es un error y no es un
mistake because I wanted to put a point on him
error porque yo quería ponerle un punto
and the example that I gave him was an example
y el ejemplo que le puse era un ejemplo
that I had I should have invented
que tenía tenía que haberme inventado
another example to make him see the point
otro ejemplo para hacerle ver el punto
that I wanted to make him see hey it is not
que yo quería hacerle ver oye pues no es
illegal to send people to look for a
ilegal mandar a la gente a buscar un
dog that has disappeared it is not harassment it
perro que se ha desaparecido no es acoso
is not illegal nor is it such and he gave him an
no es ilegal ni es tal y le puso en
example putting the names that have not
ejemplo poniendo los nombres que no
put any name no
tengan haber puesto ningún nombre ningún
real case he should have put a
caso real tenía que haber puesto un
made-up example of the law that what happens is that he
inventado de ley que lo que pasa que él
started calling me sick how could he
empezó a llamarme enfermo que como podía
do that to a girl that I don't know what
hacer eso con una niña que no sé qué
precisely that case that was being
precisamente ese caso del que se estaba
talked about in a case that hurts me
hablando en un caso que a mí me duele
because because I have lived it very closely
porque porque lo he vivido muy de cerca
okay
vale
many people know that it was
mucha gente sabe que era
knows that it is a case of lived very
sabe que es un caso de vividos muy de
closely because in that case of that
cerca por porque en ese caso de esa
person of that girl is a case that lived
persona de esa niña es un caso que vivió
very very closely it was she was my neighbor many
muy muy de cerca era era mi vecina mucha
people know it bad example here in the
gente lo sabe mal ejemplo aquí en el
neighborhood  lived through this tremendous thing
barrio se vivió esto tremendo
then it seemed that I also got
entonces como que yo me puse también
worse because there if something personal was happening to me
peor porque ahí ya si me estaba tocando
in the sense that I saw
algo personal en el sentido de que yo vi
that he was like running grabbing that
que estaba como corriendo agarrando eso
to transform and more my image
para transformar y más mi imagen
also calling me sick
además llamándome enfermo
as if I was insulting doing
como que yo estaba insultando haciendo
something insulting to that family when it
algo insultante para esa familia cuando
is the complete opposite here the whole neighborhood
es todo lo contrario aquí todo el barrio
has turned against that family because
nos hemos volcado con esa familia porque
men imagine no the case is not for
hombres imagínate no el caso no es para
less you understand me then we already
menos me entendéis entonces ya nos
got into bad shape
pusimos a las malas los dos
then we both got into bad shape
entonces ya pusimos a las malas los dos
but as I tell you it is not something that with
pero ya te digo no es una cosa que con
time you cannot talk about like
el tiempo no se puede hablar en plan la
people fight people get angry
gente se pelea la gente se enfada la
people get heated there are things there are fights
gente se calienta hay cosas hay peleas
with people that can no longer be fixed but
con gente que ya no tiene arreglo pero
with me in the one who does not fix things
conmigo en el que no arregla las cosas
I believe that even the most serious things the
yo creo que incluso las cosas más graves
most serious problems that I have
los problemas más graves que tenga yo
with people here on the internet at least
con gente aquí en internet por lo menos
even in real life is that I am a
incluso la vida real es que yo soy una
person who with myself who put
persona que conmigo quien ordenó las
things in order because he does not want time
cosas porque no quiere tiempo
sometimes it is a mistake not to be good to give
a veces es un fallo no ser bom dar
many thanks sometimes it is a mistake that
muchas gracias a veces es un fallo que
I am not I am not a resentful person is not
no soy no soy una persona rencorosa no
a person who always wants  be at
es una persona que quiera siempre estar
war with people I am a person like that does
en guerra con la gente yo es una persona
not shut things up
en plan que no se calla las cosas en
like if you have done something
plan si tú has hecho algo
if you have done something I can't shut up
si tú has hecho algo yo no me puedo
but everything we have done we
callar pero todo lo que hemos hecho lo
argue and we are fighting for a week
discutimos y estamos peleando una semana
two weeks or a year fighting no or
dos semanas o un año peleando no o
clicking the videos and if it is with someone
pulsando los vídeos y si es con alguien
from youtube or the internet or whatever okay
de youtube o de la red o lo que sea vale
cool but in the end life man life
guay pero al final la vida tío la vida
is a limited time and what we are
es un tiempo limitado y lo que estamos
living we cannot live again we cannot go
viviendo no lo podemos volver a vivir no
back as long as
podemos volver atrás el tiempo que
we are alive the time we have
estemos vivos el tiempo que tenemos
then not to live bitter or to live
entonces no para vivir amarga ni a vivir
fighting or live like that in the end you have
peleándote ni vivir tal al final tienes
to live together you have to do your
que convivir tienes que hacer sus tu
job do you understand me exemplary I don't know that you have
trabajo me entiendes ejemplar no sé que
done something to my family if you
hayas hecho algo a mi familia si me
tell me that we have not done something to my
dices que no hemos hecho algo a mi
family or you are out there publishing my
familia o estás por ahí publicando mis
personal data or things about my privacy whatever it is
datos personales o cosas de mi intimidad
something more serious is that it
lo que sea algo más grave es que me
heated me up a lot I got very angry and I
calentó muchísimo me enfadé muchísimo y
also got angrier I got angrier I got angrier
además me enfadé más me enfadé más
because then other people
me enfadé más porque luego la otra gente
took that to make news for what
agarro eso para sacar noticias para lo
other people did it was  happy and
que hizo la otra gente fue feliz y
took advantage of the fact that that girl's name went viral on Monday
aprovechó que el lunes fue viral el
to
nombre de esa chavala para
throw [ __ ] at me, save it
lanzarme [__] a mí guárdala
tremendous without limits completely without
tremendo sin límites completamente sin
limits but that worsened rather fado with
límite pero eso agravó más bien fado con
Jackie yes it's true that in the
jackie sí que es verdad que en el
live well I surely also
directo pues yo seguramente también le
said something ugly to him I don't remember surely I
dije algo feo no me acuerdo seguramente
also returned the insult I
también les devolviera al insulto
don't deny having been very heated and it's
no niego haber estado muy caliente y es
very rare that I get heated nowadays
muy raro que yo me caliente hoy en día
in the debates because normally I am already
en los debates porque de normal yo ya
with my ass as I have it already peeled
con el culo como lo tengo ya de pelado
because of the debate topic and controversial topic and so
por el tema de debate y tema polémicas y
on where only the sun is hot or it's
demás donde sólo calienta el sol o está
calm and even when they put or rather
tranquilo e incluso cuando metan o sea
cool down or when I was debating with
enfriar o cuando tuve debatiendo con
Juanjo Juan well calling me a delinquent
juanjo juan pues llamándome delincuente
'cyberstalker' and a ton of
'ciberacosador' y un montón de
information and I was calmly laughing at
informaciones y yo tranqui riéndome de
him
él
the interview that an interview or the
la entrevista que una entrevista o el
debate that we had I felt like I entered a
debate que tuvimos sentí que entre en un
place and it was an ambush that flips out you
sitio y fue una encerrona que flipa
know as much as this of course exactly like that
sabes tanto como esto claro exactamente
javi talks to a lot of people who
así javi habla con con mucha gente que
don't have similar ideas or even an
no tiene ideas parecidas o incluso una
interview
entrevista
with the debate with me in a type of
con el debate conmigo en un tipo de
occupation it's not the same forum  it's not the
ocupación no es el mismo foro no es el
same topic it could be better to put a
mismo tema lo podría mejor para poner
debate the debates with quesada with with
debate los debates con quesada con con
quesada I don't know if I've done three debates
quesada no sé si he hecho tres debates
where we were arguing and on top of that about
donde estábamos discutiendo y encima
dallas also point about dallas
sobre dallas también punto sobre dallas
and what do you know I didn't insult each other no such I think I
y que sabéis yo no nos insultamos no tal
think Fernando vila thank you very much I would have to see it
yo creo yo creo fernando ávila muchas
again I would have to come back I
gracias tendría que volver a verlo
never saw it again but I'm
tendría que volver nunca más volví a ver
going to see it again but I
pero voy a
want to remember
volver a verlo pero yo quiero recordar
that he was the one who started to turn on I'm
que fue él el que empezó a encenderse
going to miss it does
voy a faltar
n't make sense
no tiene sentido
something else says Pilar how are you
algo más dice pilar como estas
interested or doing live talking
interesarse o haciendo directo hablando
Antonia vida here talks about other things
antonia vida aquí habla de otras cosas
because I already had to multiply myself
pues porque ya me tenía que multiplicar
by two Pilar because I can't take it anymore with
por dos pilar porque ya no puedo más con
the hours that I work and with the
la de horas que trabajo y con la de
hours that I am creating content on
horas que estoy creando contenido en
all the channels and I have already said look
todos los canales y ya he dicho mira
multiply myself by 2 I have gone to a
multiplicarme por 2 he ido a un
laboratory where they multiply the
laboratorio donde me multiplican a las
people and I said look multiply by
personas y he dicho mira multiplicar por
two that this guy takes care of salt tea it was
dos que este tío se ocupe de té de sal
heard from Salcedo the kids I
se oyó de salcedo los chavales no me
had no other choice Pilar
quedaba otra pilar
but from how things evolved
pero de lo que fue evolucionando la cosa
I remember
yo recuerdo
one and the other and  climbed and climbed and in the
uno y el otro y escaló y escalando y al
end it
final
was climbing fabric example trending
fue escalando tela ejemplo trending
topic all weekend the 2 javi and
topic todo el fin de semana los 2 javi y
here I have known you since the 7 strings
aquí te conozco desde los 7 cuerdas
when I met you in person in
cuando te conocí en persona en la
Valencia one day 10,000 years and
valencia un día 10.000 años y
a person that we also
una persona que también nos
know each other in contacts we have to be
conocemos en contactos tenemos estar
quite good really if at some
bastante buenos realmente si en algún
point you know that as he assures with they
momento sabes que como asegura con
speak and rhythms that maybe
hablan y ritmos que a lo mejor tiene que
some time has to pass in time and one day it
pasar un tiempo en el tiempo y un día
arises and you talk and better if you already know
surge y habláis y mejor si ya sabes tú
that the better it is with less people you
que cuanto mejor sea con menos gente
have problems and with more people in the end
tenga movidas y con más gente al final
and in fact forgive me with rigorously this was
y de hecho me perdone con rigor esto
also the one that
también fue el
gave the coincidence no no no no in
que dio la casualidad no no no no de
fact I
hecho
was remembering good times man it's that I
estuve recordando buenos momentos tío es
only stayed with the bad
que me quedé solamente con los malos
times
tiempos
talking to him for a long time in a
hablando mucho tiempo con él en
very long time with the guy and a
muchísimo tiempo con el tío y una
person who helped my father a lot that
persona que ayudó muchísimo a mi padre
I stop the dialogue that it would be revoked to
que me pare lo diálogo que se revocaría
put the city council because he wanted the
ponerle el ayuntamiento porque quería el
judge removed it behind because we believe he was the one
juez removió a detrás porque creemos fue
who cleaned it up a bit he exposes in his time
el que limpió un poco expone en su época
because there were a lot of people in
porque había muchísima gente en la
moderation that was to feed them
moderación que era para darles de comer
apart you know in that  time and of course
aparte sabes en aquella época y claro
that had a big impact on him because he
eso le repercutió mucho a él porque él
tried, he put his chest out, he was a bit
intentó él puso el pecho él fue un poco
like me, Marbella,
como yo marbella
we had a last minute move because it turns
tuvimos una movida de últimas porque
out my father, according to what
resulta mi padre de acuerdo a lo que
happened with the young man in vanilla, outside he
pasó con el joven en el vanilla fuera él
killed I don't know who, he I don't know what, a move
mató no sé quién él no sé qué una movida
that will blow your mind and we stopped playing the
que flipas y ya dejamos de jugar el
server and everything and we left, this was the
servidor y todo y nos fuimos esta fue la
big move but within the center of the
movida gorda pero dentro del centro del
game, such and such, no, it was nothing personal and we
juego tal no no fue nada personal y nos
forgot a lot of everything that he has done,
olvidamos muchas de todo lo que ha hecho
rebound for my father, that's what I am most
rebote por mi padre es lo que más le
grateful to him for, you know, my father said,
agradezco sabes si a mí mi padre decía
I remember d
yo recuerdo d
from Rbori such and such and we fought over it and
de rébori tal y nos peleamos por eso y
then in Marbella, well, there was a misunderstanding
luego en marbella pues hubo malentendido
and he
y
contextualized it very quickly and wow, in
contextualizó muy rápidamente y vaya en
a live broadcast he says data and he will write everything
un directo dice data y escribirá todo
down, it's about and then you go out and say, hey,
trata y tú luego sales y dices oye no
let's put a little order here and
vamos a poner un poquito de orden aquí y
really, everything doesn't happen x y y z, you know,
realmente todo no pasa x y y z sabes
okay, the thing is that each of us made
vale la cosa es que cada uno hicimos
lists of people that we wanted to
unas listas de gente que queríamos que
enter, to enter, Valentn, I made my
entrar se entrase valentín yo hice mi
list and in fact this one here, look if you
lista y de hecho ésta de aquí mira si
want to put my live broadcast, we'll
quieres poner mi directo
give a point  I'm going to put it is that I don't
damos puntito le voy a poner es que no
want to leak things from the new one and another
quiero filtrar cosas del nuevo y ya otro
from the other if
del otro si
time does not pass because it is spoken with
el tiempo no pasará por que se hable con
time
el tiempo
[Music]
[Música]
and 7 I
y 7
already tell you like I get
ya te digo en plan
very heated surely if I
me caliento muchísimo seguramente si
return to the debate I will get
vuelvo en el debate me voy a calentar
very heated too maybe
mucho también tal vez
but well anyway in the end what I
pero bueno en fin al final lo que te
tell you is refined as time passes
digo se afina cuando pasa el tiempo
the less problems you have with people
cuanto menos movidas tengas con la gente
anyway it is not it is not something super super it
en fin no es no es algo súper súper no
is not something unforgivable it is not something not to be
es algo imperdonable no es algo no para
fixed clarify and that's it
arreglarse aclara y punto
or well also yes at some point we
o bien igual si también en algún momento
can talk there is something more air that they
podemos hablar hay algo más aire que
say about me we can move on to another topic
digan de mí podemos pasar otro tema
there is something more air it
hay algo más aire
would be all notable I give myself permission okay
sería todo notable me doy permiso vale
[Music]
[Música]